<resources>
    <string name="app_name">30-days-app</string>
    <string name="loading">Loading…</string>
    <string name="error">An error occurred.</string>

    <string name="stock_title1">Alphabet Inc.</string>
    <string name="stock_title2">Apple Inc.</string>
    <string name="stock_title3">AMD</string>
    <string name="stock_title4">Nvidia</string>
    <string name="stock_title5">Tesla, Inc.</string>
    <string name="stock_title6">Amazon</string>
    <string name="stock_title7">Meta Platforms</string>
    <string name="stock_title8">Microsoft</string>
    <string name="stock_title9">Cisco Systems</string>
    <string name="stock_title10">Visa Inc.</string>
    <string name="stock_title11">ExxonMobil</string>
    <string name="stock_title12">Netflix</string>
    <string name="stock_title13">PepsiCo</string>
    <string name="stock_title14">Coca-Cola</string>
    <string name="stock_title15">Walmart</string>
    <string name="stock_title16">Palantir</string>
    <string name="stock_title17">JPMorgan Chase</string>
    <string name="stock_title18">AbbVie Inc.</string>
    <string name="stock_title19">Adobe Inc.</string>
    <string name="stock_title20">Bank of America</string>
    <string name="stock_title21">Chevron Corp.</string>
    <string name="stock_title22">General Electric</string>
    <string name="stock_title23">Boeing</string>
    <string name="stock_title24">Wells Fargo</string>
    <string name="stock_title25">Pfizer</string>
    <string name="stock_title26">Costco</string>
    <string name="stock_title27">Starbucks</string>
    <string name="stock_title28">Citigroup Inc.</string>
    <string name="stock_title29">Goldman Sachs</string>
    <string name="stock_title30">Uber</string>


    <string name="stock_description1">Alphabet is the world\'s third-largest technology company by revenue, after Amazon and Apple, the largest technology company by profit, and one of the world\'s most valuable companies.</string>
    <string name="stock_description2">Apple Inc. is an American multinational corporation and technology company headquartered in Cupertino, California, in Silicon Valley. It is best known for its consumer electronics, software, and services.</string>
    <string name="stock_description3">AMD is a hardware and fabless company that designs and develops central processing units (CPUs), graphics processing units (GPUs), field-programmable gate arrays (FPGAs), system-on-chip (SoC), and high-performance computer solutions.</string>
    <string name="stock_description4">Nvidia Corporation is an American technology company headquartered in Santa Clara, California. Founded in 1993 by Jensen Huang, Chris Malachowsky, and Curtis Priem, it develops graphics processing units (GPUs), system on a chips (SoCs), and application programming interfaces (APIs) for data science, high-performance computing, and mobile and automotive applications.</string>
    <string name="stock_description5">Tesla, Inc. is an American multinational automotive and clean energy company. Headquartered in Austin, Texas, it designs, manufactures and sells battery electric vehicles (BEVs), stationary battery energy storage devices from home to grid-scale, solar panels and solar shingles, and related products and services.</string>
    <string name="stock_description6">Amazon.com, Inc., doing business as Amazon, is an American multinational technology company engaged in e-commerce, cloud computing, online advertising, digital streaming, and artificial intelligence. Founded in 1994 by Jeff Bezos in Bellevue, Washington, the company originally started as an online marketplace for books but gradually expanded its offerings to include a wide range of product categories, referred to as "The Everything Store".</string>
    <string name="stock_description7">Meta Platforms, Inc. is an American multinational technology company headquartered in Menlo Park, California. Meta owns and operates several prominent social media platforms and communication services, including Facebook, Instagram, Threads, Messenger and WhatsApp. </string>
    <string name="stock_description8">Microsoft Corporation is an American multinational corporation and technology conglomerate headquartered in Redmond, Washington. Founded in 1975, the company became influential in the rise of personal computers through software like Windows, and the company has since expanded to Internet services, cloud computing, video gaming and other fields. Microsoft is the largest software maker, one of the most valuable public U.S. companies, and one of the most valuable brands globally.</string>
    <string name="stock_description9">Cisco Systems, Inc. (using the trademark Cisco) is an American multinational digital communications technology conglomerate corporation headquartered in San Jose, California. Cisco develops, manufactures, and sells networking hardware, software, telecommunications equipment and other high-technology services and products. Cisco specializes in specific tech markets, such as the Internet of things (IoT), domain security, videoconferencing, and energy management.</string>
    <string name="stock_description10">Visa Inc. is an American multinational payment card services corporation headquartered in San Francisco, California. It facilitates electronic funds transfers throughout the world, most commonly through Visa-branded credit cards, debit cards and prepaid cards.</string>
    <string name="stock_description11">Exxon Mobil Corporation is an American multinational oil and gas corporation headquartered in Spring, Texas, a suburb of Houston. It is vertically integrated across the entire oil and gas industry, as well as within its chemicals division, which produces plastic, synthetic rubber, and other chemical products. As the largest U.S.-based oil and gas company, ExxonMobil is the seventh-largest company by revenue in the U.S. and 13th-largest in the world.</string>
    <string name="stock_description12">Netflix is an American subscription video on-demand over-the-top streaming service. The service primarily distributes original and acquired films and television shows from various genres, and it is available internationally in multiple languages.</string>
    <string name="stock_description13">PepsiCo, Inc. is an American multinational food, snack, and beverage corporation headquartered in Harrison, New York, in the hamlet of Purchase. PepsiCo\'s business encompasses all aspects of the food and beverage market. It oversees the manufacturing, distribution, and marketing of its products.</string>
    <string name="stock_description14">The Coca-Cola Company is an American multinational corporation founded in 1892. It manufactures, sells and markets soft drinks including Coca-Cola, other non-alcoholic beverage concentrates and syrups, and alcoholic beverages.</string>
    <string name="stock_description15">Walmart Inc. is an American multinational retail corporation that operates a chain of hypermarkets (also called supercenters), discount department stores, and grocery stores in the United States and 23 other countries. It is headquartered in Bentonville, Arkansas.</string>
    <string name="stock_description16">Palantir Technologies Inc. is an American publicly traded company specializing in software platforms for data mining. The company has four main operating systems: Palantir Gotham, Palantir Foundry, Palantir Apollo, and Palantir AIP. Palantir Gotham is an intelligence tool used by police in many countries as a predictive policing system and by militaries and counter-terrorism analysts, including the United States Intelligence Community (USIC) and United States Department of Defense.</string>
    <string name="stock_description17">JPMorgan Chase and Co. (stylized as JPMorganChase) is an American multinational finance corporation headquartered in New York City and incorporated in Delaware. It is the largest bank in the United States, and the world\'s largest bank by market capitalization as of 2024.</string>
    <string name="stock_description18">AbbVie Inc. is an American pharmaceutical company headquartered in North Chicago, Illinois. Its major products are: Humira (adalimumab) ($9 billion in 2024 revenues, 16% of total revenues), approved to treat autoimmune diseases including rheumatoid arthritis, Crohn\'s disease, plaque psoriasis, and ulcerative colitis and administered via injection; Skyrizi (Risankizumab) ($11.7 billion in 2024 revenues, 21% of total revenues), an interleukin-23 (IL-23) inhibitor also used to treat autoimmune diseases; Rinvoq (Upadacitinib) ($6.0 billion in 2023 revenues, 11% of total revenues), used to treat arthritis; and Botox ($6.0 billion in 2024 revenues, 11% of total revenues).</string>
    <string name="stock_description19">Adobe Inc., formerly Adobe Systems Incorporated, is an American computer software company based in San Jose, California. It offers a wide range of programs from web design tools, photo manipulation and vector creation, through to video/audio editing, mobile app development, print layout and animation software.</string>
    <string name="stock_description20">The Bank of America Corporation is an American multinational investment bank and financial services holding company headquartered at the Bank of America Corporate Center in Charlotte, North Carolina, with investment banking and auxiliary headquarters in Manhattan. It is the second-largest banking institution in the United States and the second-largest bank in the world by market capitalization, both after JPMorgan Chase. Bank of America is one of the Big Four banking institutions of the United States.</string>
    <string name="stock_description21">Chevron Corporation is an American multinational energy corporation predominantly specializing in oil and gas. The second-largest direct descendant of Standard Oil, and originally known as the Standard Oil Company of California, it is active in more than 180 countries. Within oil and gas, Chevron is vertically integrated and is involved in hydrocarbon exploration, production, refining, marketing and transport, chemicals manufacturing and sales, and power generation.</string>
    <string name="stock_description22">General Electric Company (GE) was an American multinational conglomerate founded in 1892, incorporated in the state of New York and headquartered in Boston. Over the years, the company had multiple divisions, including aerospace, transportation, energy, healthcare, lighting, locomotives, appliances, and finance. In 2020, GE ranked among the Fortune 500 as the 33rd largest firm in the United States by gross revenue. In 2023, the company was ranked 64th in the Forbes Global 2000.</string>
    <string name="stock_description23">The Boeing Company is an American multinational corporation that designs, manufactures, and sells airplanes, rotorcraft, rockets, satellites, and missiles worldwide. The company also provides leasing and product support services. Boeing is among the largest global aerospace manufacturers; it is the fourth-largest defense contractor in the world based on 2022 revenue and is the largest exporter in the United States by dollar value.</string>
    <string name="stock_description24">Wells Fargo and Company is an American multinational financial services company with a significant global presence. The company operates in 35 countries and serves over 70 million customers worldwide. It is a systemically important financial institution according to the Financial Stability Board, and is considered one of the "Big Four Banks" in the United States, alongside JPMorgan Chase, Bank of America, and Citigroup.</string>
    <string name="stock_description25">Pfizer Inc. is an American multinational pharmaceutical and biotechnology corporation headquartered at The Spiral in Manhattan, New York City. Founded in 1849 in New York by German entrepreneurs Charles Pfizer (1824–1906) and Charles F. Erhart (1821–1891), Pfizer is one of the oldest pharmaceutical companies in North America.</string>
    <string name="stock_description26">Costco Wholesale Corporation, doing business as Costco, is an American multinational corporation which operates a chain of membership-only big-box warehouse club retail stores. As of 2021, Costco is the third-largest retailer in the world, and as of August 2024, Costco is the world\'s largest retailer of beef, poultry, organic produce, and wine, with just under a third of American consumers regularly shopping at Costco warehouses.</string>
    <string name="stock_description27">Starbucks Corporation is an American multinational chain of coffeehouses and roastery reserves headquartered in Seattle, Washington. It was founded in 1971 by Jerry Baldwin, Zev Siegl, and Gordon Bowker at Seattle\'s Pike Place Market initially as a coffee bean wholesaler.</string>
    <string name="stock_description28">Citigroup Inc. or Citi is an American multinational investment bank and financial services company based in New York City. The company was formed in 1998 by the merger of Citicorp, the bank holding company for Citibank, and Travelers. Citigroup is the third-largest banking institution in the United States by assets; alongside JPMorgan Chase, Bank of America, and Wells Fargo, it is one of the Big Four banking institutions of the United States.</string>
    <string name="stock_description29">The Goldman Sachs Group, Inc. is an American multinational investment bank and financial services company. Goldman Sachs is the second-largest investment bank in the world by revenue and is ranked 55th on the Fortune 500 list of the largest United States corporations by total revenue. In the Forbes Global 2000 of 2024, Goldman Sachs ranked 23rd. It is considered a systemically important financial institution by the Financial Stability Board.</string>
    <string name="stock_description30">Uber Technologies, Inc. is an American multinational transportation company that provides ride-hailing services, courier services, food delivery, and freight transport. It is headquartered in San Francisco, California, and operates in approximately 70 countries and 15,000 cities worldwide. It is the largest ridesharing company worldwide with over 150 million monthly active users and 6 million active drivers and couriers.</string>
</resources>