<resources>
    <string name="app_name">30-days-app</string>

    <string name="stock_title1">Alphabet Inc.</string>
    <string name="stock_title2">Apple Inc.</string>
    <string name="stock_title3">AMD</string>
    <string name="stock_title4">Nvidia</string>
    <string name="stock_title5">Tesla, Inc.</string>
    <string name="stock_title6">Amazon</string>
    <string name="stock_title7">Meta Platforms</string>
    <string name="stock_title8">Microsoft</string>
    <string name="stock_title9">Broadcom Inc.</string>
    <string name="stock_title10">Visa Inc.</string>
    <string name="stock_title11">Mastercard</string>
    <string name="stock_title12">Netflix</string>
    <string name="stock_title13">PepsiCo</string>
    <string name="stock_title14">Coca-Cola</string>
    <string name="stock_title15">Walmart</string>
    <string name="stock_title16">Capital One</string>
    <string name="stock_title17">JPMorgan Chase</string>
    <string name="stock_title18">Samsung Electronics</string>
    <string name="stock_title19">Adobe Inc.</string>
    <string name="stock_title20">Oracle Corp.</string>
    <string name="stock_title21">IBM</string>
    <string name="stock_title22">McDonald\'s</string>
    <string name="stock_title23">Boeing</string>
    <string name="stock_title24">Honeywell</string>
    <string name="stock_title25">Pfizer</string>
    <string name="stock_title26">Costco</string>
    <string name="stock_title27">Starbucks</string>
    <string name="stock_title28">BMW AG</string>
    <string name="stock_title29">Take-Two, Inc.</string>
    <string name="stock_title30">Uber</string>


    <string name="stock_description1">Alphabet is the world\'s third-largest technology company by revenue, after Amazon and Apple, the largest technology company by profit, and one of the world\'s most valuable companies.</string>
    <string name="stock_description2">Apple Inc. is an American multinational corporation and technology company headquartered in Cupertino, California, in Silicon Valley. It is best known for its consumer electronics, software, and services.</string>
    <string name="stock_description3">AMD is a hardware and fabless company that designs and develops central processing units (CPUs), graphics processing units (GPUs), field-programmable gate arrays (FPGAs), system-on-chip (SoC), and high-performance computer solutions.</string>
    <string name="stock_description4">Nvidia Corporation is an American technology company headquartered in Santa Clara, California. Founded in 1993 by Jensen Huang, Chris Malachowsky, and Curtis Priem, it develops graphics processing units (GPUs), system on a chips (SoCs), and application programming interfaces (APIs) for data science, high-performance computing, and mobile and automotive applications.</string>
    <string name="stock_description5">Tesla, Inc. is an American multinational automotive and clean energy company. Headquartered in Austin, Texas, it designs, manufactures and sells battery electric vehicles (BEVs), stationary battery energy storage devices from home to grid-scale, solar panels and solar shingles, and related products and services.</string>
    <string name="stock_description6">Amazon.com, Inc., doing business as Amazon, is an American multinational technology company engaged in e-commerce, cloud computing, online advertising, digital streaming, and artificial intelligence. Founded in 1994 by Jeff Bezos in Bellevue, Washington, the company originally started as an online marketplace for books but gradually expanded its offerings to include a wide range of product categories, referred to as "The Everything Store".</string>
    <string name="stock_description7">Meta Platforms, Inc. is an American multinational technology company headquartered in Menlo Park, California. Meta owns and operates several prominent social media platforms and communication services, including Facebook, Instagram, Threads, Messenger and WhatsApp. </string>
    <string name="stock_description8">Microsoft Corporation is an American multinational corporation and technology conglomerate headquartered in Redmond, Washington. Founded in 1975, the company became influential in the rise of personal computers through software like Windows, and the company has since expanded to Internet services, cloud computing, video gaming and other fields. Microsoft is the largest software maker, one of the most valuable public U.S. companies, and one of the most valuable brands globally.</string>
    <string name="stock_description9">Broadcom Inc. is an American multinational designer, developer, manufacturer, and global supplier of a wide range of semiconductor and infrastructure software products. Broadcom\'s product offerings serve the data center, networking, software, broadband, wireless, storage, and industrial markets.</string>
    <string name="stock_description10">Visa Inc. is an American multinational payment card services corporation headquartered in San Francisco, California. It facilitates electronic funds transfers throughout the world, most commonly through Visa-branded credit cards, debit cards and prepaid cards.</string>
    <string name="stock_description11">Mastercard Inc., stylized as MasterCard from 1979 to 2016 and as mastercard from 2016 to 2019, is an American multinational payment card services corporation headquartered in Purchase, New York. It offers a range of payment transaction processing and other related-payment services (such as travel-related payments and bookings).</string>
    <string name="stock_description12">Netflix is an American subscription video on-demand over-the-top streaming service. The service primarily distributes original and acquired films and television shows from various genres, and it is available internationally in multiple languages.</string>
    <string name="stock_description13">PepsiCo, Inc. is an American multinational food, snack, and beverage corporation headquartered in Harrison, New York, in the hamlet of Purchase. PepsiCo\'s business encompasses all aspects of the food and beverage market. It oversees the manufacturing, distribution, and marketing of its products.</string>
    <string name="stock_description14">The Coca-Cola Company is an American multinational corporation founded in 1892. It manufactures, sells and markets soft drinks including Coca-Cola, other non-alcoholic beverage concentrates and syrups, and alcoholic beverages.</string>
    <string name="stock_description15">Walmart Inc. is an American multinational retail corporation that operates a chain of hypermarkets (also called supercenters), discount department stores, and grocery stores in the United States and 23 other countries. It is headquartered in Bentonville, Arkansas.</string>
    <string name="stock_description16">Capital One Financial Corporation is an American bank holding company founded on July 21, 1994, and specializing in credit cards, auto loans, banking, and savings accounts, headquartered in Tysons, Virginia, with operations primarily in the United States. It is the ninth largest bank in the United States by total assets as of September 30, 2024, the third largest issuer of Visa and Mastercard credit cards, and one of the largest car finance companies in the United States.</string>
    <string name="stock_description17">JPMorgan Chase and Co. (stylized as JPMorganChase) is an American multinational finance corporation headquartered in New York City and incorporated in Delaware. It is the largest bank in the United States, and the world\'s largest bank by market capitalization as of 2024.</string>
    <string name="stock_description18">Samsung Electronics Co., Ltd. is a South Korean multinational major appliance and consumer electronics corporation founded on 13 January 1969 and headquartered in Yeongtong District, Suwon, South Korea. It is currently the pinnacle of the Samsung chaebol, accounting for 70% of the group\'s revenue in 2012, and has played a key role in the group's corporate governance due to cross ownership.</string>
    <string name="stock_description19">Adobe Inc., formerly Adobe Systems Incorporated, is an American computer software company based in San Jose, California. It offers a wide range of programs from web design tools, photo manipulation and vector creation, through to video/audio editing, mobile app development, print layout and animation software.</string>
    <string name="stock_description20">Oracle Corporation is an American multinational computer technology company headquartered in Austin, Texas. Co-founded in 1977 in Santa Clara, California, by Larry Ellison, who remains executive chairman, Oracle Corporation is the fourth-largest software company in the world by market capitalization as of 2025.</string>
    <string name="stock_description21">International Business Machines Corporation (using the trademark IBM), nicknamed Big Blue, is an American multinational technology company headquartered in Armonk, New York, and present in over 175 countries. It is a publicly traded company and one of the 30 companies in the Dow Jones Industrial Average. IBM is the largest industrial research organization in the world, with 19 research facilities across a dozen countries.</string>
    <string name="stock_description22">McDonald\'s Corporation, doing business as McDonald\'s, is an American multinational fast food chain. As of 2024, it is the second largest by number of locations in the world, behind the Chinese chain Mixue Ice Cream and Tea.</string>
    <string name="stock_description23">The Boeing Company is an American multinational corporation that designs, manufactures, and sells airplanes, rotorcraft, rockets, satellites, and missiles worldwide. The company also provides leasing and product support services. Boeing is among the largest global aerospace manufacturers; it is the fourth-largest defense contractor in the world based on 2022 revenue and is the largest exporter in the United States by dollar value.</string>
    <string name="stock_description24">Honeywell International Inc. is an American publicly traded, multinational conglomerate corporation headquartered in Charlotte, North Carolina. It primarily operates in four areas of business: aerospace, building automation, industrial automation, and energy and sustainability solutions (ESS). Honeywell also owns and operates Sandia National Laboratories under contract with the U.S. Department of Energy.</string>
    <string name="stock_description25">Pfizer Inc. is an American multinational pharmaceutical and biotechnology corporation headquartered at The Spiral in Manhattan, New York City. Founded in 1849 in New York by German entrepreneurs Charles Pfizer (1824–1906) and Charles F. Erhart (1821–1891), Pfizer is one of the oldest pharmaceutical companies in North America.</string>
    <string name="stock_description26">Costco Wholesale Corporation, doing business as Costco, is an American multinational corporation which operates a chain of membership-only big-box warehouse club retail stores. As of 2021, Costco is the third-largest retailer in the world, and as of August 2024, Costco is the world\'s largest retailer of beef, poultry, organic produce, and wine, with just under a third of American consumers regularly shopping at Costco warehouses.</string>
    <string name="stock_description27">Starbucks Corporation is an American multinational chain of coffeehouses and roastery reserves headquartered in Seattle, Washington. It was founded in 1971 by Jerry Baldwin, Zev Siegl, and Gordon Bowker at Seattle\'s Pike Place Market initially as a coffee bean wholesaler.</string>
    <string name="stock_description28">Bayerische Motoren Werke Aktiengesellschaft, trading as BMW Group, is a German multinational conglomerate manufacturer of luxury vehicles and motorcycles headquartered in Munich, Bavaria, Germany.</string>
    <string name="stock_description29">Take-Two Interactive Software, Inc. is an American video game holding company based in New York City founded by Ryan Brant in September 1993. The company owns three major publishing labels, Rockstar Games, Zynga and 2K, which operate internal game development studios. Take-Two created the Private Division label to support publishing from independent developers, though it sold the label in 2024.</string>
    <string name="stock_description30">Uber Technologies, Inc. is an American multinational transportation company that provides ride-hailing services, courier services, food delivery, and freight transport. It is headquartered in San Francisco, California, and operates in approximately 70 countries and 15,000 cities worldwide. It is the largest ridesharing company worldwide with over 150 million monthly active users and 6 million active drivers and couriers.</string>
</resources>